https://www.radioactive.fm/privacy-policy/

1. Our Privacy Policy
We respect the privacy of all of the users and suppliers who use the RadioActive.FM app. We are committed to all customers to protect their personal information. Our privacy policy is based on the Information Privacy Principles in the Privacy act 1993. This privacy policy applies to all users and suppliers in relation to our service.
2. Variation
We reserve the right to vary this policy at any time, effective immediately upon posting on our website www.RadioActive.FM. This privacy policy was last updated on Monday 16 05 2019.
3. How information is collected by us and how it is used
Using the RadioActive.FM app requires users to sign up for the RadioActive.FM loyalty scheme. We collect users’ names, email addresses, gender and date of birth.
User information will be made available to our suppliers (Listed in the app under Chosen Few and Associated Discounters) as anonymous demographic information.
Users will be sent our monthly email newsletter, which always includes the option to unsubscribe.
The QR code scanning system collects information about which users are using which discounts and when. This information will be used for the continuing improvement of our service to identify the offers and suppliers that are most popular with our users.
On occasion our premium suppliers (Or Chosen Few) can request information about top users of their discounts, so that these users can be rewarded with exclusive prizes and offers. These will be communicated using the app’s push notification system and can be redeemed using the QR code scanning system.
We will not use or disclose your personal information in any way, other than in accordance with this policy, the terms referred to above or the privacy act 1993.
4. Security of information collected
We employ procedural and technological measures to protect your personally identifiable information.
5. Access and Correction
Under the privacy act 1993, you have the right to seek access to the information we hold about you and to correct that information if it is incorrect. You may access or change the information we have collected about you by placing your request in writing and sending your request to us at;
RadioActive.FM 98.5FM
PO Box 11971
Manners Street
Wellington
New Zealand
Or you can email us at support@radioactive.fm
6. Definitions
In these terms and conditions the following expressions shall have the following meanings, unless the context requires otherwise.
“RadioActive.FM app” means the RadioActive.FM smartphone application owned and operated by Radio Active FM Limited
“RadioActive.FM” is the name of our loyalty scheme which is accessed through the RadioActive.FM app
“User” means anyone who has downloaded the RadioActive.FM app and therefore signed up to RadioActive.FM
“Supplier” means any retailer that has agreed to participate in our loyalty scheme, RadioActive.FM
“You/your” refers to the user or supplier (as appropriate) using the RadioActive.FM app
[TITLE]
[DATE] [TIME]
[DESCRIPTION]
dddd MMMM d, yyyy
title
[TITLE]
[DATE] [TIME]
[DESCRIPTION]
dddd MMMM d, yyyy
title
